<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Jeffrey A. Zyjeski - Speculative Fiction Author on Jeffrey A. Zyjeski - Author</title>
    <link>https://agent.zyjeski.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Jeffrey A. Zyjeski - Speculative Fiction Author on Jeffrey A. Zyjeski - Author</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://agent.zyjeski.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Biography</title>
      <link>https://agent.zyjeski.com/bio/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agent.zyjeski.com/bio/</guid>
      <description>Professional Background Jeffrey A. Zyjeski brings a unique perspective to speculative fiction through his extensive background in law, government relations, and contemplative practice. With a Juris Doctor from the University of Connecticut School of Law, he has spent over 25 years navigating the complex intersections of legal frameworks, corporate interests, and governmental policy.
His professional experience spans multiple sectors, providing him with deep insights into how institutional power operates and how technological innovation intersects with regulatory and ethical considerations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://agent.zyjeski.com/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://agent.zyjeski.com/contact/</guid>
      <description>Literary Agent Inquiries Literary agents and publishers are encouraged to contact Jeffrey A. Zyjeski directly regarding &amp;ldquo;The Karmic Protocol&amp;rdquo; and future projects.
Email: jeff@zyjeski.com
Response Time: Typically within 48 hours for professional inquiries
For Agents and Publishers When contacting regarding manuscript submissions, please include:
Your agency or publishing house affiliation Specific interest in &amp;ldquo;The Karmic Protocol&amp;rdquo; or other projects Preferred format for submission materials (query, synopsis, sample pages) All standard industry submission formats are accommodated, and materials can be provided electronically or via traditional mail as preferred.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
